MAY

LIU



OBJECTIVE

Searching for the opportunity to bring 17+ years experiences with R&D (Research and Development) product management, Web design, full stack development, server maintenance, wechat development for cross-border marketing, incorporating critical thinking, problem solving. And deliver rich product marketing solution to web sites, mobile applications and e-commerce applications.



EDUCATION

MASTER SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE | Northwestern Polytechnic University 2010.9-2011.9, AND 2013.9 – 2015.4 GPA: 3.9



EXPERIENCE

Project Manager & Full Stack Web Developer | Gomay Group (US) 2015 - PRESENT

Leading the development and customer support teams. Application design and development. Implementing, merging, testing and publishing the application updates, delivering new application features, designing and planning new features.

CTO | Beijing Yiyou Technology CO., (Start-Up Company in tourism industry)

2011-2013

Leading the development team, manage project scope and deliverable to support business goals in collaboration.

IT Manager | Aoji Education Group (Top study abroad industry in China)

2001-2010

- . Designed and Set up Aoji Education Group Website.
- . As a part of website team, worked with Marketing and Sales Department to design from scratch user interfaces based on wireframes.
- . Worked with programmers to Set up Office Assistant System.
- . Provided the data of web analytics for Marketing and sales Department.
- . Set up Customer Relationship Management System(CRM).
- . Based on the development of company, adding new functions into OA System and CRM System.
- . Managed and rebuilt the network and server room.
- . Built Call Center System for 33 branches(cites) in China.